I'm very sorry to say this, that Brazil is doing poorly
and will continue to do poorly.
They can only do well when they're working with us.
Without us, they will fail just as others have failed.
It's true.
Next year, the United States will celebrate
the 250th anniversary of our glorious independence,
a testament to enduring power and American freedom and spirit.
We will also be proudly hosting the 2026 FIFA World Cup
and, shortly thereafter, the 2028 Olympics,
which is going to be very exciting.
I hope you all come.
I hope that countless people from all over the globe
will take part of these great —
these will be great celebrations of liberty and human achievement
and that, together, we all can rejoice
in the miracles of history that began in July 4 —